[
    {
    "option1": "I have be going.",
    "option2": "I am been going.",
    "option3": "I have been going.",
    "option4": "I am being going.",
    "question": "আমি যেতে থাকছি",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "I shall be going.",
    "option2": "I shall been going.",
    "option3": "I will be going.",
    "option4": "I shall going.",
    "question": "আমি যেতে থাকবো",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "I was going.",
    "option2": "I has been going.",
    "option3": "I have been going.",
    "option4": "I had been going.",
    "question": "আমি যেতে  থেকেছিলাম",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Had I been going ?",
    "option2": "Have I been going ?",
    "option3": "Have I  going ?",
    "option4": "Have I was going ?",
    "question": "আমি কি যেতে থাকছি ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Will I be going ?",
    "option2": "Shall I be gone ?",
    "option3": "Shall I be going ?",
    "option4": "Shall I been going ?",
    "question": "আমি কি যেতে থাকবো ?",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Had I been going ?",
    "option2": "Had I be going ?",
    "option3": "Have I been going ?",
    "option4": "Was I been going ?",
    "question": "আমি কি যেতে  থাকছিলাম ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "I have gone.",
    "option2": "I had gone.",
    "option3": "I was gone.",
    "option4": "I had been gone.",
    "question": "আমি গেলাম",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Had I going ?",
    "option2": "Had I gone ?",
    "option3": "Had I went ?",
    "option4": "Have I gone ?",
    "question": "আমি কি গেলাম ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "I can have gone.",
    "option2": "I could have going.",
    "option3": "I could have go.",
    "option4": "I could have gone.",
    "question": "আমি যেতে পারতাম",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Could I have gone ?",
    "option2": "Could I have going ?",
    "option3": "Can I have gone ?",
    "option4": "Did I have gone ?",
    "question": "আমি কি যেতে পারতাম ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "I would have went.",
    "option2": "I was have gone.",
    "option3": "I would have gone.",
    "option4": "I would had gone.",
    "question": "আমি যেতে পারতাম",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Would I had gone ?",
    "option2": "Would I have gone ?",
    "option3": "Was I have gone ?",
    "option4": "Had I have gone ?",
    "question": "আমি কি যেতাম ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "I should have go.",
    "option2": "I should gone.",
    "option3": "I should have went.",
    "option4": "I should have gone.",
    "question": "আমার যেতে পারা উচিৎ ছিল",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Should I had gone ?",
    "option2": "Should I have gone ?",
    "option3": "Shall I have gone ?",
    "option4": "Should I  go ?",
    "question": "আমার কি যেতে পারা উচিৎ ছিল ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "I may have gone.",
    "option2": "I may had gone.",
    "option3": "I  have gone.",
    "option4": "I may have go.",
    "question": "আমি যেতে পারতাম",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "May I have go ?",
    "option2": "May I had gone ?",
    "option3": "May I have gone ?",
    "option4": "May I have to go ?",
    "question": "আমি কি যেতে পারতাম ?",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "I can not but going.",
    "option2": "I can not but to go.",
    "option3": "I can not but goes.",
    "option4": "I can not but go.",
    "question": "আমি না গিয়ে পারি না",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "I can not help go.",
    "option2": "I can not help going.",
    "option3": "I can not helped going.",
    "option4": "I could not help going.",
    "question": "আমি না গিয়ে পারি না",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    }
]